Guide to the Franklin Bowditch Dexter Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Subject Files, Circa 1860-1920; Series II; 1' 8" (4 boxes)
  - Volumes
    - List of alumni, Undated (Box 24, Folder 15-16)
    - Notebook: citations for historical research and lists of Dexter's books, Undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Notes for a subject index (unidentified), Undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Research notes: Clapham, Henock, Theological Axioms, copies of documents, State Papers Charles I, Domestic, State Papers James I, Domestic, Unidentified, 1893 February 22, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Webster's Dictionary Supplement
    - Correspondence, 1860-1884, undated
      - Bancroft--Bliss (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Bolton--Butler (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Carpenter--Cooper (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Davidson--Durfee (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - Gage--Holzer (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Jones--Luken (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Mahn--Mendenhall (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Merriam, G.C.--Miller (Box 25, Folder 27)
      - Neff--O'Reilly (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Parker--Pulsifier (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - Philips, George Morris (Box 25, Folder 30)
      - Redway--Sweeney (Box 25, Folder 31)
      - Thiese--Witte (Box 25, Folder 32)
      - Unidentified (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - "Scientific Nomenclature," by George H. knight, manuscript, definitions, 1867 July 29 (Box 26, Folder 34-36)
    - Illustrations, notebook [William A. Wheeler?], 1871 March 21 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Notes for entries, Undated (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Clippings, 1876-1879, undated (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Additional entries and corrections, notebook, [1876-1879?] (Box 26, Folder 40)